They want to become travel writers.
Question 25. is the speaker's advice on winning a loyal audience?
College English Test, Band 6, Part 2, Listening Comprehension, Section A,
Directions. In this section, you will hear two long conversations.
At the end of each conversation, you will hear four questions.
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once.
After you hear a question, you must choose the best answer from the four choices
marked A, B, C, and D.
Then, mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet 1 with a single line through the
center. Conversation 1.
How's your dissertation going?
I'm proofreading my first draft, and will submit it to my professor tomorrow.
Oh, I haven't even started writing mine yet, so I'm really worried about finishing
by the end of next semester.
You mean you haven't even begun yours yet?
The final draft is due in five months.
Of course I've started it, but I can't get to the writing yet, as I haven't found
enough resources to use, so I'm still researching the topic.
Maybe the problem is the way you're doing your research.
I started by talking to my professor about where to look for information, and based
on that, I found books in the library, and a lot of reputable journal articles on
the internet. I've tried all that, but don't have enough to write the dissertation,
as my department's minimum length is 70 pages.
I think the problem is that my topic isn't viable.
And honestly, my professor did warn me at the beginning that I might not be able to
find enough material, but I was so interested in the topic that I didn't let his
advice deter me.
Well, I suggest you find a new topic.
After all, our professors are here to guide us, so it's best to listen to them.
In retrospect, I wish I had listened to him.
But I didn't, and now I don't want to give up my topic, as I've already invested so
much time and energy.
If you're committed to your current topic, maybe you could make some adjustments,
rather than abandoning it completely.
What is your topic?
It's depictions of femininity in folklore from the south of the country.
That's pretty narrow.
You could find more material if you made the topic broader, maybe by including other
kinds of depictions.
Broadening the topic is a great idea.
I'll start by including folklore from other regions of the country.
Questions 1 to 4 are based on the conversation you have just heard.
Question 1. What does the woman say about her dissertation?
Question 2. What does the man say about his professor?
Question 3. What does the woman say about her professor?
Question 4. What do we learn the woman will do to complete her dissertation?
Conversation 2. Today on Book Talk, we're lucky enough to host John Robbins and
discuss his new book, Why Americans Are Fat and How We Can Lose Weight.
John isn't just a respected writer.
He's also one of the rare celebrity authors writing about science today.
Thanks for having me, Rebecca.
But I'm hardly a celebrity.
That's very modest of you to say, considering that your four books have sold a total
of 7 million copies worldwide, and they've been translated into 12 different
languages. What makes people so fascinated with your work?
Well, people read my books because more than 60 of Americans are overweight or
obese, and other countries are facing similar problems.
Basically, we all want to know how to fix things.
We certainly do.
I've read your new book, and it's fabulous, especially when it comes to the way you
make difficult science easy for laymen to understand.
That's no small achievement.
I'm glad to hear you find my work accessible, because I was worried when I wrote it
that discussing the science might make the book more suited for a specialist
audience. My last book was written primarily for the medical community, but this
time I want to help ordinary people take control of their weight.
And how do you suggest they do that?
Can you give us the basics of your advice for people who want to lose weight?
Briefly, I argue that every person needs to consider their metabolism and eat what
suits their body's needs.
I don't advocate one single diet.
Some people should eat more carbohydrates than others, and different people need
different amounts of protein and fat.
you do have some recommendations for everyone, including eating 10 servings of
vegetables and 3 of fruit a day.
We'll talk about those recommendations next, but now we need to take a short break
for a message from our sponsor.
Questions 5 to 8 are based on the conversation you have just heard.
Question 5. What does the woman say about the man in her introduction?
Question 6. What has motivated the man to write his books?
Question 7. Who does the man say his last book was mainly written for?
Question 8. What does the man recommend people do?
Question the recommend people to do?
Section B. Directions.
In this section, you will hear two passages.
At the end of each passage, you will hear three or four questions.
Both the passage and the questions will be spoken only once.
After you hear a question, you must choose the best answer from the four choices
marked A, B, C, and D.
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet 1 with a single line through the
center. Passage 1.
Stress is often depicted as negative, but research shows that moderate amounts of it
can be beneficial for your brain and your body.
First, the benefits for the brain.
Studies have shown that short periods of stress can actually bolster cognitive
functioning. Researchers discovered that placing rats in a stressful situation for
just a few hours doubled the growth of new brain cells.
The rats also did better on a memory test later on.
Scientists think the same thing happens in humans.
But how does stress improve memory?
It's simple. When your brain cells multiply, your memory can improve.
Viewed from a biological perspective, this makes sense because animals that are
better at remembering dangerous situations can avoid them in the future.
If an animal encounters a predator and escapes, for example, it's important to
remember where and when that encounter happened.
Experts assert that the same principle applies to Now, let's turn to how stress
benefits the body.
This may come as a surprise to laymen,
but experts say that stress can keep you from getting sick.
Scientists concede that chronic stress can make you more prone to illness.
But research shows that short periods of stress can actually provide some protection
against getting sick because it increases your immune functioning.
One study shows that rats that experienced brief stress had a surge of immune cell
response, which makes the immune system better prepared to fight illness.
For humans, there's even evidence that experiencing stress before getting vaccinated
could help make vaccines more effective.
Questions 9 to 11 are based on the passage you have just heard.
Question 9. What did researchers discover about rats placed briefly in a stressful
situation? Question 10.
Why do people tend to have clearer memories of dangerous situations they have
encountered? Question 11.
What do scientists believe chronic stress can do?
Passage 2. many managers and people who work in leadership positions, dealing with
emails is a dilemma.
It's likely the unpredictable, uncontrollable, and ongoing nature of day -to -day
email in terms of volume, importance, and urgency contributes to their levels of
anxiety and to diminished leadership skills.
That's because it's not unusual for many leaders to prioritize email management over
people management.
An obsession with managing their inbox prevents them from dealing with their
employees. As a result, they ignore the issues that might only be mild problems at
first, until, unfortunately, they inevitably transform into a major problem or
crisis by virtue of neglect.
As leaders, they are expected to motivate and inspire their team in pursuit of
longer -term strategic goals,
and also, less ambitiously but more practically, to monitor their daily output, to
set clear expectations, and to give regular feedback.
When presented with a choice between the appeal of their inbox and other more
important activities, many sacrifice the latter.
Daily email demands have a negative impact on their goal progress.
This is because leaders must divert resources from other tasks to check, filter, and
respond to emails.
The solution is cultivating self -control, which is like a muscle.
It can be strengthened or improved over time through exercise.
Some suggestions include making space in your diary for the only periods during
which you'll be checking emails, setting a timer for yourself so you don't become
distracted by your inbox for too long, turning off email alerts so you're not
interrupted by them.
Questions 12 to 15 are based on the passage you have just heard.
Question 12. What does the speaker say is a common problem with managers?
Question 13. What may happen when managers ignore minor problems?
Question 14. What are leaders expected to do in pursuing their strategic goals?
Question 14. 14.
Question 15. How can a manager best avoid being distracted by email?
Section C. Directions.
In this section, you will hear three recordings of lectures or talks, followed by
three or four questions.
The recordings will be played only once.
After you hear a question, you must choose the best answer.
From the four choices, marked A, B, C, and D.
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet 1, with a single line through the
center. Recording 1.
In last week's lecture, we talked about the problems caused by poor eating habits,
focusing on how medical professionals are trying to solve these problems.
Today, we'll continue with the topic, but focus on research from a different field.
Marketing. Now, what can marketing tell us about improving nutrition?
Well, a team of marketing professors has studied the importance of the visual aspect
of food, and how that influences food choices.
Those marketing experts assert that the impact of the appearance of food is greater
than we might presume.
And might hold the key to encouraging better eating.
So, how important is the appearance of food?
Research shows that just seeing an appealing photograph of a hamburger in an
advertisement, for example, can cause individuals to imagine the taste or smell of
that hamburger. This can make them more likely to purchase and consume it.
Of course, that's the point of advertisements, so isn't that a good thing?
Well, the marketing professors argue that this is actually a problem, because the
combination of pleasing aesthetics of and easy access to unhealthy foods, such as
hamburgers and pizza, may be contributing to a worldwide health crisis.
In fact, statistics show that 39 of all adults in the world weigh too much, and
another 13 are obese.
Now, as we discussed last time, medical professionals have tried to fight the
obesity epidemic by focusing on the nutrients found in different foods, emphasizing
things like But they've had limited success.
The marketing professors believe that the real solution to obesity is making food
look appealing and focusing on the pleasure of both looking at and eating that food.
That pleasure can be used as a tool to promote healthy food choices.
In fact, the research done by the team showed that associating healthy food with
pleasant images, experiences, and emotions led to greater interest in purchasing or
eating it. This is a better strategy, they claim, than reminding consumers that a
certain food is good for them.
But are they right?
Well, the researchers cited a marketing campaign designed to reverse the sales
decline of carrots.
The campaign didn't emphasize the carrots' healthy qualities, but embraced their
beauty and the pleasure derived from eating them.
For example, the ads focused on the bright, beautiful orange color and crisp texture
of the carrots.
The campaign led to an impressive increase in product sales of more than 10%.
The researchers believe that other companies could bolster sales of healthy foods
with similar ads, depicting their products as attractive and a source of pleasure.
Question 16 to 18 are based on the recording you have just heard.
Question 16. What does the speaker say a team of marketing professors has studied?
Question 17. How have medical professionals tried to fight obesity?
Question 18. What can other companies learn from the example of the carrot promotion
campaign? Recording 2.
The household cleaning products industry really began to take off in the 1950s.
Prior to that, resourceful housewives who had grown up in a less prosperous era
relied on substances that they used in their kitchens, such as vinegar used to clean
windows. Today, the household cleaning products industry is worth billions of
dollars a year and is dominated by large global companies.
In recent years, many countries have witnessed a surge in the number of small
businesses and companies offering more environment -friendly cleaning products.
And they're doing good business, too.
One reason for this is that consumers are becoming more aware of environment and
sustainability issues.
They also want to make their home a safe place, free from toxic chemicals.
The third reason is people's of and knowledge about technology has never been
greater. In the past, people might have been skeptical of a new product claimed to
be able to achieve amazing cleaning results.
But they now have faith in technology's ability to do what was once thought
impossible. There is perhaps no better example of this than a patented cloth sold by
one company which remarkably uses only water rather than traditional cleaning
products. The company claims its cloth lifts, traps, and removes dirt and bacteria.
And considering that people don't see these products in shops or advertised on TV or
in the press, it has been a pretty steep rise.
Many of the people behind these companies began testing the viability of their
products by selling them at local markets.
Then, in many cases, customers are doing the marketing for these products by leaving
threads of comments on social media praising their virtues.
There are also TV shows and books dedicated to maintaining home tidiness and
cleanliness and the benefits of having a clean home.
Having a safe and clean home might be one thing people feel they can control in an
increasingly out of control world.
And there are social media celebrities.
One woman in Britain has become a social media sensation with more than 2 million
followers for her Cleaning Tips page.
Questions 19 to 21 are based on the recording you have just heard.
Question 19. What does the speaker say about the cleaning products industry in
recent years? Question 20.
Why are newly developed cleaning products selling well?
Question 21. What are some customer's customers doing to help promote non
-traditional cleaning products?
Recording 3. Throwing spare change into a fountain is a time -honored ritual.
Throw a into the water, and your wish might come true.
But all that money has to go somewhere.
Otherwise, the growing piles of pennies, quarters, and euros could clog up the
fountain's works. Today, I'm going to talk about where all the coins go.
Well, the coins collected can go to all sorts of different places, from fountain
maintenance to charity or public service.
In New York City, for example, coins collected from fountains and public parks often
go towards the fountain's maintenance itself, though entrepreneurs who don't mind
getting their hands wet often get to it first.
There are over 50 beautiful, decorative display fountains in New York City parks.
They are cleaned by the park's staff every few weeks.
But most of the coins have already been removed by entrepreneurial New Yorkers, and
there is not a significant amount left to be collected.
Other cities, though, can pull in a much more serious haul.
Take, for example, Rome's famous Trevi Fountain.
For hundreds of years, visitors have thrown coins over their shoulder into the
fountain to ensure that they will return.
So many tourists tossing coins that Roman officials have the fountain cleaned every
night, reportedly getting as much as $4,000 in loose change from around the world
each day. Most of the money collected each night goes towards running a supermarket
for the needy, and collecting that cash is serious business.
Roman officials have been known to be tough on anyone caught skimming coins from the
fountain. In one case in 2005, police arrested four fountain cleaners after they
were spotted slipping coins into their own pockets after collecting them.
Authorities finally caught one notorious thief named Thomas Morgan and banned him
from the fountain after he fished out thousands of dollars in change over 34 years
using a magnetic stick.
For the most part, money collected from privately owned fountains in the United
States also goes to charity.
The fountain in New York City's Bryant Park is owned and operated by a not -for
-profit corporation, which puts the cash collected by cleaners towards the
fountain's own maintenance.
Tens of thousands of dollars in coins removed from wishing wells, fountains, and
ponds in Florida's Walt Disney World are donated each year to support foster
children living in the state.
Whether or not your wish comes true after tossing a coin into a fountain,
you can rest assured knowing that the change is likely going to someone who needs
it. Questions 22 to 25 are based on the recording you have just heard.
Question 22. What problem might be caused by the growing piles of coins in
fountains? Question 23.
What does the speaker say about the coins collected from New York City's park
fountains? Question 24.
What do we learn about the money collected from Rome's Trevi Fountain?
does What does collected Trevi